This is how to build a polyarket trading
bot using OpenClaw. And over the past
three days, I've gotten a lot of
questions around how did you build the
Poly Market trading bot that just works
on its own that you just wake up and
it's made you $15 in your sleep.
And thinking about this, I thought the
best way of showing you how I've built
it is by literally showing you how I've
built it, by showing you the prompts
that I used to work on this bot with
Max, my AI agent. So, that being said,
let's let's get started with literally
the first prompt that I used on this
exact project, which was I will give you
a list of posts I found about us making
money. And then I proceeded to send him
a list of all the articles I managed to
find that popped on my feed about Poly
Market uh bots and OpenClaw
[clears throat] making money together.
And from that, it started telling me,
"Got it. let me pull these tweets. It
pulled all of the different tweets. It
read through them. It understood what
they're about. And next up, I told him,
"Let's do the same. Ask them to make
money." He always in in in my AI agents
max fashion, he said, "Hell yes."
Looking at what they're doing, they're
basically three money streams. And he
categorized the different articles.
Polymarket referrals. Those are people
who just preach that they can make
money, but the real way that they're
making money is through the poly market
referral that they put in their
articles. So, they're not really making
money. Then there's copy trading bot
referrals as well. Then there's actual
bot trading. Some are genuinely running
bots on Poly Market 15inut Bitcoin
Ethereum markets. Here's what we can do.
This is the perfect play. We already
started the the bot. I gave up on it a
couple of days ago. Basically was just a
thought that I had back then. I didn't
want to put much time into it. I was
like, "Hey, listen. We have the
groundwork. This is what we can do." I
wanted to to to run the polyarket
referral link thing at first because
that's what most of the articles were
using. They weren't actually trading. I
was like, "No, I want us to run the same
bot." He's like, "Got it. Let me check
what we've already built and what we
need to get the same setup. Ah, I found
the markets. There are some short-term
markets. Five minute, 15 minute, hourly,
four hours. Let me check if we can
actually access and trade these. Bingo.
I can see 15minute markets over here.
From that,
let me see. So, from that, that was its
entire response that I was just showing
you. And it finishes by build from
scratch. I can write a simple Python bot
using our existing setup. What do you
want me to do? And that's where I told
it, what do you think? I want you to
lead this entirely.
So this is me getting you and giving you
a glimpse over the behind the scenes of
how I think when I develop my bot. I
don't want you to look at this and
literally copy paste what I said to it
word by word because odds are it's going
to reply to you differently.
You're not going to get the exact same
results. Instead, I want you to start
thinking about
how do I think and how can I help my AI
agent
get to the goal I desire. You are the
operator. Your AI agent is the engine.
With that being said, this is what it
gave me. All right, I'll own this.
Here's my call. My recommendation phase
one, let's validate. Let's spend this
week on validation. Which is why in all
my videos I say week one is about us
testing. Is about my AI agent learning.
Let's fund this with $100. Let's track P
profit and loss for three to five days.
Phase two, let's scale and or pivot.
Phase three, let's document, which is
exactly what I did. I literally followed
its advice. What I need from you? I need
a poly market account funded. I need a
VPS preference. Do you want to run this
on your Mac mini or on digital ocean
droplet? And what's your risk tolerance?
And I answered these questions for it.
And it got started. So that's it.
over here it was saying boom it we went
through a long setup phase of
probably like an hour or two long where
I was figuring out how to create Poly
Market API so that it has access to my
Poly Market account. I was figuring out
how to fund the the wallet that it
needed uh because Poly Market uses a
different wallet than the one you sign
in with. I was figuring out how to give
it full access to the things it needed
and it was helping me out through that.
And then we finished by send me the URL
of the market that you want to start
with. I sent it the Bitcoin up and down
15 minutes market. Found it. That market
just ended. Let me get the full details
and find the next active one. It found
it. The current market up down the
pattern is so on and so forth. Let me
update the bot and do a test trade.
Minimum is five shares. Let me increase
the bet. First trade placed. And that
was literally my first tweet. I set up
my Poly Market bot wrong because what it
ended up doing is it placed the bet as
soon as the market opened. It was still
a 5050 chance. Literally, you can see 47
cents,
52 cents. It was literally a coin flip
that he was betting on. He didn't
understand at that time that we needed
to wait till the last minute. And
although this was a coin flip, he
managed to make the right decision. So,
he still managed to make $20 off of his
first literal bet. We're truly living in
the future.
But from that, I asked him, is this how
we make money based on the articles I
sent you? And he's like, honestly, not
quite. From those articles, the real
edge is exploiting the lag between
Binance and chain link. For those of you
who don't know, uh the way Poly Market
works, it fetches the prices here.
Actually, why am I bothering explaining
when it's literally explaining right
here? Poly Market results based on chain
link price feed, but chain link updates
slower than Binance. So, the play is
watch Binance in real time. See Bitcoin
moving up hard. Chain link hasn't
updated yet. Poly market odds are stale.
Buy up cheap before odds adjust. Chain
link catches up. You win. Want me to
rebuild the bot with the chain link lag
exploit? Yes, please. It rebuilt it with
chain link arbitrage bot working.
And then after that I asked it how can I
check on our progress man and see how
much we're making the trades etc. And
that birthed this next post that I made
which was Max HQ. It literally went up
and it created me this whole app uh with
more than just polyarket tracking. It
allows me to see how my Poly Market bot
is doing, how my hyperlquid bot is
doing, what I have on my agenda today,
what it sent me as briefs, what tasks
have I assigned it to it. And that was
literally the first post. Finally found
a way to pay for my claw subscription.
That being said, I sent it Matic. I
asked it to learn how to autoclaim on
its own uh all of its winnings and it
launched Sniperbot version two. here it
was making some mistakes as well uh
which mainly were that
the lag detection wasn't quite working
well. It made some losses. I asked it
how can we what can we learn from these
losses and it spun up uh V2 new strategy
records price at start of window snipes
in last 30 seconds compares current
versus start price so on and so forth.
So, it spun up a new strategy after the
losses it made. Perfect. Also, why was
there an order? Why wasn't there an
order in the last 15 minutes? This was
more me trying to understand how it
works because I myself hadn't understood
its full logic yet. And it literally
just told me, you lit don't have to
guess. You don't have to make your life
hard. You can literally just ask it for
things and it will answer you.
But with that being said, that was that
is the last slide. So that was the
thought process that I used in building
this. There was a V1, there was a V2 and
yesterday it managed to lose five trades
consecutively when the market went
extremely volatile and a repeat scenario
happened from the screenshot where I was
like, hey, what happened here and what
can we learn? and it adjusted itself and
it's now at its third version. Again,
week one is about testing,
hypothesizing, and getting proof of
concept, proof that this actually works.
And then week two is about scaling it
from there.
Again, I don't want you to look at this
and take the exact same prompts
expecting the exact same results.
I want you to take away
the strategies you use in thinking when
you speak to open claw when you speak to
your AI agent. What information do you
give it?
What goal do you define for it? How well
do you define the goal and the
parameters for it to re to reach and
achieve that goal? I hope this video has
helped. This is quite literally how I
built the bot. So, I hope this answers
your questions.